foreign
[Music]
plan anytime anywhere with the Manulife
mobile app the Manulife mobile app
allows you to submit claims on the go
view your balances download your
benefits card and more let's Dive Right
In and see how it works based on your
mobile device open app store or Google
Play Store search Manulife mobile and
download the app after launching the
Manulife mobile app sign in with your
Manulife ID and password you can even
enable Biometrics for an easier sign-in
then select your group benefits account
need to register click on set up your
Manulife ID
and you'll be redirected to our
registration page
you'll need your plan contract number
certificate number and some personal
information have questions about
Manulife ID visit manulife.ca and search
Manulife ID support to reach our help
center
once you have your Manulife IDs set up
and then sign into your account you'll
see all the options from submitting a
claim to viewing your benefits coverage
but that's not all you can see the
status of your claims find a health care
provider jump to the Vitality app and
more
the Manulife mobile app makes managing
your benefits easy and secure
[Music]